<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dialogue>
	<portrait>Isaac Happy</portrait>
	<speaker>Alex</speaker>
	<question speaker="Isaac" value = "Yo. What up dog?">
		<answer label = "Not much bro. You?">
			<text>Not much man. What's up with you?</text>
			<speaker>Isaac</speaker>
			<text>You know. Buisness. This whole update thing has been good. Lotsa people looking for a way to take their minds off it.</text>
			<label>update?</label>
			<speaker>Alex</speaker>
			<question speaker="Isaac" value = "What do you think is going on?">
				<answer label = "God">
					<text>Clearly the lord is working his will upon the world.</text>
					<portrait>Isaac Meh</portrait>
					<speaker>Isaac</speaker>
					<question value = "Are you sure?">
						<speaker>Alex</speaker>
						<answer label = "Yes">
							<text>Yes. I have no doubts.</text>
							<label>father</label>
							<speaker>Isaac</speaker>
							<text>Well. You should go talk to Father Owens the next town over then. He'll probably have stuff you'd find interesting.</text>
							<text>You can find the road there in the north west area, through the woods. You'll know its the right one cause it turns into a dirt road after a while.</text>
							<jump>goodbye</jump>
						</answer>
						<answer label = "No">
							<text>Well, no. I'm not completely sure.</text>
							<speaker>Isaac</speaker>
							<text>Well. You should go talk to Charlotte Owens. She'll probably have stuff you'd find interesting.</text>
							<text>You can find her in the retirement home on the western side of town. Its a huge brown building. Can't miss it.</text>
							<jump>goodbye</jump>
						</answer>
					</question>
				</answer>
				<answer label = "Nothing.">
					<text>This update means nothing. Life goes on. You know?</text>
					<speaker>Isaac</speaker>
					<text>I hear you man. And if it is something, what are we gonna do about it, right?</text>
					<jump>goodbye</jump>
				</answer>
				<answer label = "Dunno">
					<text>I dunno man. But I'll tell you what man. I'm freaking out about it.</text>
					<speaker>Alex</speaker>
					<question speaker="Isaac" value = "Well, you want something to make it go down easier?">
						<answer label = "nah.">
							<text>Nah. I'm ok. I wanna know whats going on. Not ignore it.</text>
							<label>answers</label>
							<text>Well. You should go talk to Chief Duffy. I heard a rumour that he knows what's going on. Some sort of government thing.</text>
							<text>You can find him in the North east area. But if you hit the college campus you've gone too far!</text>
							<jump>goodbye</jump>
						</answer>
						<answer label = "Yes!">
							<text>Hell yes. I need to get my mind off this shit.</text>
							<text>Well. You should go talk to Mike. I heard he's setting up an insane party at the college campus.</text>
							<text>You can find him in the frat house on campus. The campus is in the north east area, and the frat is on the north western corner of campus.</text>
							<jump>goodbye</jump>
						</answer>
					</question>
				</answer>
			</question>
		</answer>
		<answer label = "Worrying">
			<text>I'm worrying about this whole update thing. Especially Megan. I don't like to think that something might happen to her.</text>
			<question speaker="Isaac" value = "Well, what are you gonna do about it?">
				<answer label = "Dunno">
					<text>I don't know man. I gotta figure it out though. I guess I'm gonna go figure out what's going on.</text>
					<jump>answers</jump>
				</answer>
				<answer label = "Use friends">
					<text>I guess I'm just gonna have to count on friends. I know you'll keep her safe man.</text>
					<question speaker="Isaac" value = "And the rest of the gang too. You know we're family.">
						<answer label = "Of course">
							<text>Thats true. I know all you guys have my back.</text>
							<speaker>Isaac</speaker>
							<jump>update?</jump>
						</answer>
						<answer label = "sure">
							<text>Yeah... I guess.</text>
							<portrait>Isaac Meh</portrait>
							<jump>update?</jump>
						</answer>
						<answer label = "No">
							<text>I trust you man. The rest of them... No. Not with Megan.</text>
							<portrait>Isaac Angry</portrait>
							<question speaker="Isaac" value = "What do you mean man?">
								<answer label = "Your family">
									<text>Its your family. Not mine man.</text>
									<speaker>Isaac</speaker>
									<text>Fuck you man. It was supposed to be our family.</text>
									<quit/>
								</answer>
								<answer label = "Its Megan">
									<text>Its Megan man. I trust them with my life everyday. But this is Megan man. I barely trust her to myself.</text>
									<speaker>Issaac</speaker>
									<portrait>Isaac Meh</portrait>
									<text>Alright. Alright. I hear yeah.</text>
									<jump>update?</jump>
								</answer>
							</question>
						</answer>
					</question>
				</answer>
				<answer label = "pray">
					<text>Pray. The lord will provide for us.</text>
					<jump>father</jump>
				</answer>
			</question>
		</answer>
	</question>
	<label>goodbye</label>
	<speaker>Alex</speaker>
	<text>Alright man. I'll do that.</text>
	<speaker>Isaac</speaker>
	<text>Cool. Be careful out there. You hear? I don't wanna end up taking care of Megan.</text>
	<speaker>Alex</speaker>
	<text>You got it bro. See you later.</text>
	<quit/>
</dialogue>
